Hello.
どうもこんにちは
yes.
はい
It's been about 2 years.
2年ぶりぐらいだね
How have you been?
元気だった?
fine.
元気
I really wanted to meet you.
会いたかったんだよね、俺は本当に
I've always wanted to meet you.
ずっと会いたかった
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I like sex.
エッチ好き
It's the same as always.
相変わらずだね
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
Sex two years ago was amazing.
2年前のセックスは すげえよかったな
You don't remember, right?
覚えてないでしょ?
Look here.
こっち見て
I like it, it's cute.
いいね、かわいいね
Look at me.
見つめてよ
I said let's have sex.
エ ッチしようって言ったね
Let's have sex.
エッチしよう
Hello.
どうもこんにちは
Yes, hello.
はい、こんにちは
It's raining.
雨ですね
It was really humid.
湿気やばかったね
Was it humid?
湿気やばかった?
It was extremely humid.
湿気やばかった
How do you feel on a rainy day?
雨の日ってどんな気分になる?
bothersome.
めんどくさい
A troublesome day?
めんどくさい日?
It's been a while since we met.
久しぶりだね、会うのね
How many years has it been since?
何年ぶりぐらいですか?
It's been about 2 years.
2年ぶりぐらいだね
How have you been?
元気だった?
fine.
元気
I really wanted to meet you.
会いたかったんだよね、俺は本当に
I've always wanted to meet you.
ずっと会いたかった
I want to meet you, and I'm wondering when we can meet.
会いたくてね、 いつ会えるのかなと思ってさ
It's far from where I live.
住んでるところは遠いじゃん
That's why we didn't get to meet each other very often,
だからなかなか会えなかったんだけど、
It means we finally met.
やっと会えたってことでね
It's cute no matter what.
やりかわらずかわいいですね
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
nice.
いいね
Are you still naughty?
相変わらずエッチなの?
Well, I don't know.
えー、分かんない
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I like sex.
エッチ好き
It's the same as always.
相変わらずだね
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
The sex we had two years ago was amazing.
2年前のセックスは、 すげえ良かったな
You don't remember, do you?
覚えてないでしょ
I remember, I remember, I totally remember.
覚えてる覚えてる、全然覚えてるよ
No, it was really intense at that time.
いや、あの時すげえだって激しかったもん
Have you had a child?
子供できちゃった?
I did cum inside though.
中に出しちゃったけど
Did you make it?
できたの?
It hasn't been done yet.
できてないよね
Even I let it out until it reached my uterus.
俺でも中に子宮に届くまで出しちゃったからね
No, I can see your pants.
いや、パンツ見えてる
That's amazing.
すげえ良いな
Can you see it?
見えてる?
I can see it, I can see it.
見えてる見えてる
cute.
かわいい
Ah, suddenly pants?
ああ、もういきなりパンツ?
Ah, it's transparent.
あ、透けてるね
Isn't it transparent?
透けてない?
Isn't the hair showing through?
毛透けてない?
The hair is transparent.
毛透けてるじゃん
Oh, it's transparent.
え、透けてるよ
nice.
いいね
This makes a great picture.
これすごい絵になる
It'll be a picture.
絵になるよ
It makes a great picture.
すごい絵になる
What have you been up to lately?
最近何やってるの?
I only play games.
ゲームばっかやってるな
Do you want to play games?
ゲームをたく?
It's not a game.
ゲームはなもんね
No, I really like the style.
いや、ホントスタイルいいよね
I gained weight.
太った
I'm not fat.
太ってないよ
It won't change much.
あんま変わんないじゃん
So I thought I'd send it to the side.
じゃあ横送るって思って
It won't change at all.
全然変わんないじゃん
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
Let's take a look from below.
下から見ちゃおう
I feel like I'm getting far away.
遠ざかってしてる感じ
copper?
どう?
From below this.
この下から
Do you feel distant?
遠ざかってしてる感じ?
Be early.
早いで
It's so warm.
あんま暖かいね
warm.
暖かい
Isn't it warm?
あんま暖かくね?
warm.
暖かい
Is it closed?
閉めてる?
Isn't it closed?
閉めてない?
It's closed, right?
閉めてるね、ちょっと
nice.
いい ね
Shall we sit down then?
じゃあ座っちゃおうか
No, it's cute.
いや、かわいいね
nice.
いいね
When was the last time you had sex?
最近いつセックスしたの?
When was your first experience?
初めての経験いつ?
17?
Where was it?
どこであったの?
Cub four.
カブフォー
Really?
本当に?
Seriously?
マジか?
It's normal.
普通だね
普通だよ
Didn't you do it outside?
外でやらなかったの?
It's outside.
外だね
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌なんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look here.
こっち見て
I like it, it's cute.
いいね、かわいいね
Look at me.
見つめてよ
Did I say let's have sex?
エッチしようって言った?
Let's have sex.
エッチしよう
nice.
いいね
It's cute.
かわいいね
So, can I start teasing you now?
じゃあ、もういじめていっていいですか?
Is it okay to bully you?
いじめていっていい?
yes.
はい
Is it okay?
いいの?
As always.
いつものように
Can I do it?
やっていい?
Like before.
前みたいに
Can I do it like before?
前みたいにやっていい?
where are the boobs
おっぱいどこにある
of?
の?
It's soft, as always.
柔 らかいね、相変わらず
Are you connected?
繋がってんのか?
It's connected, isn't it?
繋がってんのね
one piece.
ワンピース
Well then, your hair is long.
じゃあ、 髪長いよ
thank you.
ありがとう
Can you feel my breasts?
おっぱい感じる?
Yeah.
うん
It's so soft.
すげー柔らかい
My boobs came out.
おっぱい出てきた
Get a little excited.
ちょっと興奮してくれ
It's already up.
もうアップだよ
Very close.
めっちゃ近い
Your breasts are up.
お っぱいアップだよ
Look?
見て?
No.
いやだ
What does it look like?
どんな感じに映ってるか
You're watching, right?
見てるでしょ
No way.
いやだー
This is how my breasts look.
自 分のおっぱいはこうやって見えてる
It's so cute, you're standing next to me.
かわいいね、近くに立ってくるの
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいの?
Nearby.
近くに
Does that feel good?
そこが気持ちいいの?
Breasts, breast lenses.
おっぱい、おっぱいレンズ
cold?
冷たい?
cold.
冷たい
It's hitting the lens.
レンズに当たってるよ
Let's go home.
帰ってみよう
Okay.
いいよ
Can it be 4 o'clock?
4時になっていい?
Come here again.
またこっち来て
Can I sleep now?
今寝てていい?
tight?
きつい?
It's tough, isn't it?
きついよね
Let's be a little slanted.
ちょっと斜めになろうか
terrible.
やばい
expensive.
高い
I wonder if I'm doing it over my pants.
パンツの上からやってるかな
long time no see.
久しぶり
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Should it be stronger?
もっと強いほうがいい?
It hurts if you hit it too hard.
あんまり強く当てると痛いから
Shall I pull it out?
抜いちゃおうか
So let's take it all out?
じゃあ全部抜いちゃう?
I left out too much.
あんまり抜いちゃったね
Can I guess?
当てていい?
This angle is really good.
このアングルすごいいいんだよね
ERROR
当てちゃう?
Does it look like a hole?
穴に見える?
I would like to see the angle as well.
アングルも見せてほしい
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That's the best.
それ最高
This is dangerous.
やばいこれ
It's amazingly packed.
すげえパックリ
I could see almost everything.
お ま く丸見えたよ
It's so beautiful.
すげえおまく綺麗じゃん
Look.
ほら
Which is better?
どこがいい?
Look here.
こっち見て
I'll guess.
当てちゃうよ
good?
いい?
Then just open it yourself.
じゃあおまく自分で開いて
Puff it with both hands.
両手でパックリ
Is your heart beating?
心臓してる?
Is it getting across?
伝わってる?
In your hand.
手に
terrible.
やばい
My hands are touching.
手が当たってる
here?
ここ?
Kuri-chan?
クリちゃん?
Kuri-chan's hand is on me.
クリちゃん手が当たってる
This is terrible.
やばいよ
My hands are touching.
手が当たってる
It's very accurate.
めっちゃ当たってる
A lot of hands are on it.
いっぱい手が当たってる
My hands are touching.
手が当たってる
Now, let's see it all.
じゃあその丸見え
Is it better to be weaker?
もっと弱いほうがいい?
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いてよ
With both hands.
両手で
This way
こっち
Look.
見て
I'm starting to get naughty though.
エ ッチになってきたけど
I don't want you to settle down.
落ち着いて欲しくない
Shall we go?
行っちゃう?
Make it feel more comfortable.
もっと気持ちいいやつにして
I'll do something that feels more comfortable.
もっと気持ちいいやつやっちゃうよ
What is that?
何それ?
this.
これ
I'm pulling it out.
抜いてる
You're pulling it off really well.
上手く抜いてるじゃん
Look.
ほ ら
Do it crackly.
パチパチやって
This is coming out well.
これが上手く抜いてる
This is terrible.
これやばいよ
This is dangerous.
これやばいやつ
The one that goes inside.
中入っちゃうやつ
I'm about to go inside this
もうこの中入っちゃうや
One.
つ
After entering, I decided to proceed here.
入 ってなおかつ、 こっちで進めるっていう
double.
ダブル
With your feet.
足で
I said it was too thin.
薄くて言ってしまった
No, no.
いいやだな
copper?
どう?
What happened?
どうなった?
terrible.
やばい
Look.
ほら
Check crossing.
チェック交差
A mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃ
terrible.
やばい
This is terrible.
やばいよ、これ
Look.
ほ ら
He says it's a mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃだって言ってる
It's so fast.
めっちゃ早い
This way.
こっち
Look here, carefully.
こ っち見て、ちゃんと
Look here.
こっち見て
Is it really like that?
めっちゃそうなの?
What do you think?
どうなの?
Are you coming in?
入ってくる?
Don't stop.
止めちゃダメだよ
I'm hitting like crazy.
めっちゃくちゃ打ってる
Okay.
いいよ
Great, I'm sleeping.
すげー、寝てる
I'm really asleep.
め っちゃ 寝てる
I hear a strange seal.
めやらしいシールが聞こえる
what happened?
どうしたの?
Next, the one that is dangerous to have.
次、持ってやばいやつ
This is dangerous.
これ、やばいやつ
It's a dangerous thing to have.
持ってやばいやつね
This is something I've been wondering about for a while.
これさっき気になってたやつだよ
put in?
入れる?
It looks like a penis.
おちんちんみたいだよ
What do you think of this?
どうでしょ、これ
This is it.
これね
I really hate it though.
めっちゃ嫌いなんだけど
Really.
め っちゃ
It's a bit of a mess so I'll go right in.
なんか、ぐちゃぐちゃだからすぐ入る
Look.
ほ ら
How far can it go?
どこまで入るの?
Can't get into it?
あんま入んない?
this?
これ?
Hold on to me, please.
ちょっと押さえてくれ、自分
Well, come on, I'm going to go take a shower.
じゃあ、ちょっとさ、 俺、シャワー行くからさ
Just masturbate, then.
オナにしてて、じゃあ
Just like that.
そのまま
Something I always do.
いつも、いつもやるやつ
Like I always do.
いつ もやるように
yes.
はい
A little more?
もうちょい?
Is it getting worse?
もうちょくなってきた?
It's really dripping.
すげえ垂れてる
A naughty sticker is dripping down.
やらしいシールが垂れてきてる
Awesome.
すげえ
terrible.
やばい
Can't get out?
抜けない?
After all, the big feeling of the skin on my hands
やっぱり手肌の大きな気持ち
Become.
にな る
copper?
どう?
It's so warm.
すげえ温かい
It's warm.
温かいね
It feels really warm.
なんか、めっちゃ温かい
I'm gargling.
うがくてきてる
Become one of a kind.
つっちみちになる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Hey.
ねえ
It feels so good.
あんま、気持ちいい
Hey.
ねえ
yes.
はい
Well then, let's lick it.
じゃあ、つっちみち舐めよっか
Lick it.
舐めよ
I feel like I can start licking it a little
ちょっと舐めだせる感じに
hey.
ね
Don't you want one?
つ っちみち欲しくなんないの?
This camera.
こっちのカメラ
Well, let's use this mirror for a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっとこの鏡使おう
Look, you can see yourself.
ほら、自分映ってるでしょ
Next time, let's sit on the sofa.
次、ソファー座ろうね
Well then,
じゃあ、
Yeah.
うん
I guess I'll go cut it.
切 っていこっかな
Are you sleeping?
寝てる?
Yeah.
うん
Then go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝て
Did you sleep once?
一回寝ました?
Let me sleep.
寝かせて
sleep?
寝る?
A-chan, let me sleep.
あーちゃん、寝かせて
Let me sleep.
寝かせて
Is it even better?
つっちみちもっといい?
It's in.
入ってるよ
So, let me sleep.
それで、 寝きさせて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ah, this color is amazing.
あー、これすげー色
here?
ここ?
Very colorful.
めっちゃ色
Is it difficult?
むずい?
difficult?
難しい?
My legs hurt so bad.
めっちゃ足が痛い
It hurts a lot, but my leg is sore.
めっちゃ痛いけど、 つった足
My legs are really cramped right now.
めっちゃ足つってる、今
My legs hurt so bad.
めっちゃ足が痛い
went?
行った?
Wait a minute, I haven't removed it yet.
ちょっと待って、まだ抜いてない
I'll pull it out.
抜くよ
It's really hard to pull it out.
抜くとめっちゃむずいんだよ
Here.
こ この
Okay, let's go.
よし、いくぜ
3、2、1
Good.
よいしょ
Oh, it came out, it came out.
おー、出てきた出てきた
Oh, dripping dripping.
あー、垂れた垂れた
It's dripping.
垂れてきたよ
Please show me your face.
ちょっと顔見せてね
Kamanko.
かまんこ
It's gone, inside.
いっちゃった、中に
child.
子供
Maybe I had a child.
子供できた、多分
What should I do?
どうする?
I had a child.
子供できちゃった
Aren't I sweaty?
俺、汗やばくない?
Are you drawing?
描いてる?
Didn't you draw it?
描いてなくね?
What is it?
なんだよ
Why aren't you drawing?
なん で描いてないの?
I'm drawing.
描 いてる
It came out.
出た
It came out great.
すげー出てきた
That's terrible.
やばいね
how was it?
どうだった?
Your anus is huge.
アナルでかいな
Oh, that's a lie.
え、嘘だよ
That's a lie.
嘘だよ
How was it over there?
あっち、どうでした?
how was it?
どうだった?
Finally, clean only the tip.
最後、先っぽだけお掃除してよ
Cleaning, last.
お 掃除、ラスト
Like Rena Tanaka.
田中玲奈みたいに
Rena Tanaka is reducing it.
田中玲奈ちゃんが減らしてくれてる
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくないの?
I think it's super cute, but...
超可愛いと思うんだけど、俺は
copper?
どう?
What will you do?
ど んなにする?
sour.
酸っぱい
That's a very realistic feeling.
すげーリアルな感想だね
All that's dripping down here is my sweat.
ここまで垂れてるやつ、全部俺の汗だね
Finally, please give us your thoughts.
じゃあ最後、感想お願いします
What do you think?
何感想?
how was it?
どうだった?
Try it.
やってみて
It's often hot because I'm wearing a mask.
マスクしてるからよく熱い
Let me know your thoughts.
ちょっと感想聞かせてよ
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
Will we do it again?
またやる?
Let's cosplay, next time.
コスプレしよう、今度
Have you ever done it?
やったことある?
Safe is good.
セーフがいい
But don't take it off from the beginning.
でも、最初から脱いじゃダメ
Until the end.
最後まで
All the way to the end?
最後もずっと?
Let's do that.
やろうよ、それ
Shall we do it?
やっちゃう?
I think people who see it will say so.
見てくれる人、言うと思うんだよ
Take this.
これ をね
Last word.
一言最後
It's okay, just say.
大丈夫、一言
Look at my guy.
私のやつを見てください
After all, this is going to be a work of art.
一応これは作品になるわけだからさ
With myself.
自分とね
Me and us?
自分と俺らのか
So something, something against this.
それで何か、これに対して何か
Please watch a lot.
たくさん見てください
How can I do this?
これどんなにしていいの?
Please give it to me as much as possible.
いっぱいお前にしてください
So let's believe that there will be another time.
じゃあ次もまたあることを信じよう
Well then, cosplay.
じゃあコスプレね
Well then, thank you for your hard work.
じゃあお疲れ様
bye bye.
バイ バイ
Wave.
手振って
good night.
おやすみなさい
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ